Neha Erasmus African Union High Level Implementation Panel Papers MS207
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Negotiations records, 2010 -- 2013; MS207.002; 911 Digital Object(s)
  - August 2012 negotiations, MS207.002.00558
    - AUHIP Matrix of Progress on Post-Secession Issues, 2012-09-18; MS207.002.00715
    - Draft Statement, 2012-09-20; MS207.002.00716
    - AUHIP Matrix of Progress on Post-Secession Issues, 2012-09-21; MS207.002.00717
    - Agreement on Certain Economic Matters Merged, 2012-09-24; MS207.002.00718
  - October 2012 negotiations, 2010 -- 2012; MS207.002.00719
    - Abyei, 2012; MS207.002.00720
      - Implementation Plan Based on the PSC Communique of 24 October 2012 review BM2, 2012-10-28; MS207.002.00721
      - Draft AUHIP Abyei soft borders plan, 2012-10-30; MS207.002.00722; Lortan, Fiona
      - Next Steps, 2012-11-01; MS207.002.00723; Afako, Barney
      - Implementation Plan Based on the PSC Communique of 24 October 2012 - Draft 1, 2012-11-01; MS207.002.00724
      - AUHIP Draft Proposal for Next Steps on Abyei, 2012-11-20; MS207.002.00725
      - Update to AUHIP, 2012-11-20; MS207.002.00726
      - AUHIP Draft Government of Sudan - Proposal for Next Steps on Abyei, 2012-12-01; MS207.002.00727
      - AUHIP Draft Proposal for Next Steps on Abyei, 2012-12-01; MS207.002.00728
    - Final report, 2012; MS207.002.00729
      - AUHIP Comprehensive Report task allocations, 2012-11-05; MS207.002.00730
      - AM letter to Haile Menkerios/UN map coordinates, 2012-11-06; MS207.002.00731
    - Implementation matrix, 2012; MS207.002.00732
      - Implementation Matrix for Sudan-South Sudan Agreements, 2012-10-17; MS207.002.00733
      - Implementation Matrix for Sudan-South Sudan Agreements - Draft 2, 2012-10-17; MS207.002.00734
      - Implementation Matrix - Draft 3, 2012-10-18; MS207.002.00735
      - Implementation Matrix - Draft 4, 2012-10-19; MS207.002.00736
      - AUHIP Draft Implementation Matrix - Draft 5, 2012-10-22; MS207.002.00737
      - AUHIP Draft Implementation Matrix- Draft 6, 2012-10-22; MS207.002.00738
    - Planning for six weeks, 2012; MS207.002.00739
      - Draft AUHIP Abyei soft borders plan, 2012-10-30; MS207.002.00740
      - Draft Calendar, 2012-10-31; MS207.002.00741
    - Two areas, 2012; MS207.002.00742
      - Two areas HCFA - Draft 2, 2012-10-10; MS207.002.00743
      - 2A Scan, 2012-10-22; MS207.002.00744
      - Translation Two Areas Doc, 2012-10-22; MS207.002.00745
      - Unofficial Translation, 2012-10-22; MS207.002.00746
      - PSC Minutes, 2012-10-25; MS207.002.00747
    - AUHIP Plan of Action Jan 2010, 2010-01; MS207.002.00748
    - Update, 2012-10-14; MS207.002.00749
    - How did the negotiators and principals present the agreement to, 2012-10-16; MS207.002.00750
    - Update on Situation in Sudan after Agreements, 2012-10-17; MS207.002.00751
    - Assessment on how agreement received in South Sudan, 2012-10-18; MS207.002.00752
    - AUHIP Comprehensive Report outline - Draft 1, 2012-10-20; MS207.002.00753
    - AUHIP Draft Next Steps Memo, 2012-10-20; MS207.002.00754
    - Non Paper on Possible Next Steps on Abyei, 2012-10-20; MS207.002.00755
    - AUHIP letter UNISFA/General Tadesse Tesfaye, 2012-10-31; MS207.002.00756
    - AUHIP letter Haile Menkerios/UN, 2012-11-01; MS207.002.00757
    - AUHIP letter UNISFA/General Tadesse Tesfaye, 2012-11-01; MS207.002.00758
    - AUHIP letter Haile Menkerios/UN, 2012-11-06; MS207.002.00759
  - November 2012 negotiations, MS207.002.00760
    - Briefing on JPSM Meeting, 2012-11-06; MS207.002.00761
    - Secretariat Minutes, 2012-11-06; MS207.002.00762
    - Terms of Reference PMC Acting Chair: Sudan-South Sudan Petroleum Monitoring Committee, 2012-11-13; MS207.002.00763
    - Update on oil issues, 2012-11-18; MS207.002.00764
    - Abdul Mohammed letter UNDP PMC Chair, 2012-11-19; MS207.002.00765
    - Abdul Mohammed letter UNECA PMC Chair, 2012-11-19; MS207.002.00766
    - Security Update, 2012-11-20; MS207.002.00767
    - Update to the AUHIP, 2012-11-20; MS207.002.00768
    - AUHIP Invite, 2012-11-27; MS207.002.00769
    - AUHIP Invite John Kuong/MoD, 2012-11-27; MS207.002.00770
    - Update, 2012-12-03; MS207.002.00771
  - December 2012 negotiations, MS207.002.00772
    - Briefing, 2012; MS207.002.00773
      - AUHIP Update, 2012-11-20; MS207.002.00774
      - Other issues, 2012-11-20; MS207.002.00775
      - Draft Report sudan south sudan December 2012, 2012-12; MS207.002.00776
      - AUHIP Update, 2012-12-09; MS207.002.00777
      - Draft Briefing for AUHIP, 2012-12-10; MS207.002.00778
      - Draft Security Briefing for AUHIP, 2012-12-10; MS207.002.00779
    - Joint Political and Security Mechanism, 2012; MS207.002.00780
      - Implementation Activities - Matrix Version 6, 2012-12-18; MS207.002.00781
    - Peace and Security Council report, 2012; MS207.002.00782
      - Update on Abyei - Draft, 2012-11-20; MS207.002.00783
      - Draft Briefing for AUHIP, 2012-12-09; MS207.002.00784
      - Draft Briefing for AUHIP, 2012-12-09; MS207.002.00785
      - Draft Briefing for AUHIP, 2012-12-10; MS207.002.00786
      - AUHIP Draft Report PSC Consolidated Comments, 2012-12-11; MS207.002.00787
      - AUHIP Draft Report PSC, 2012-12-11; MS207.002.00788
      - AUHIP Report to the PSC, 2012-12-12; MS207.002.00789
      - AUHIP Report to the PCS, 2012-12-14; MS207.002.00790
      - AUHIP Report to the PSC - Draft, 2012-12-14; MS207.002.00791
    - Abdul Mohammed Invite Government of Sudan - MoD, 2012-11-12; MS207.002.00792
    - Abdul Mohammed Invite AJOC, 2012-12-10; MS207.002.00793
    - Abdul Mohammed Invite Government of the Republic of South Sudan - AJOC, 2012-12-10; MS207.002.00794
    - Abdul Mohammed Invite Government of Sudan - AJOC, 2012-12-10; MS207.002.00795
    - Abdul Mohammed Invite Idriss Abdel Gadir, 2012-12-10; MS207.002.00796
    - Abdul Mohammed Invite Pagan Amum, 2012-12-10; MS207.002.00797
    - Abdul Mohammed Invite UNISFA FC, 2012-12-10; MS207.002.00798
    - Abdul Mohammed Invite UNISFA FC, 2012-12-10; MS207.002.00799
    - AUHIP Invite LN, 2012-12-10; MS207.002.00800
    - Abdul Mohammed Invite Government of the Republic of South Sudan - MoD, 2012-12-12; MS207.002.00801
    - Letter from Abdul Mohammed to Pagan Amum - Special flight, 2012-12-12; MS207.002.00802
    - Letter from Abdul Mohammed to Pagan Amum - Special flight, 2012-12-12; MS207.002.00803
    - Abdul Mohammed invite to SPLMN, 2012-12-13; MS207.002.00804
    - AUHIP invite to SPLMN, 2012-12-13; MS207.002.00805
    - Pagan Amum Meeting 14 Mile Interpretation, 2012-12-13; MS207.002.00806
    - Suggested Agenda LNP Meeting, 2012-12-13; MS207.002.00807
  - January 2013 negotiations, 2012 -- 2013; MS207.002.00808
    - Invitations, 2013; MS207.002.00809
      - AUHIP invite implementation GoRSS 1, 2013-01-07; MS207.002.00810
      - AUHIP invite implementation GoRSS 2, 2013-01-07; MS207.002.00811
      - AUHIP invite implementation GoS, 2013-01-07; MS207.002.00812
      - AUHIP invite implementation GoS, 2013-01-07; MS207.002.00813
      - AUHIP invite JPSM GoRSS, 2013-01-07; MS207.002.00814
      - AUHIP invite JPSM GoS, 2013-01-07; MS207.002.00815
      - AUHIP invite JPSM GoRSS, 2013-01-11; MS207.002.00816
      - AUHIP invite JPSM GoS, 2013-01-11; MS207.002.00817
    - Joint Political and Security Mechanism, 2012 -- 2013; MS207.002.00818
      - Implementation Activities, 2012-12-18; MS207.002.00819
      - Implementation Plan, 2013-01-15; MS207.002.00820
      - Approved by the Joint Political and Security Mechanism (JPSM), 2013-01-15; MS207.002.00821
      - Extraordinary Meeting of the Joint Political and Security Mechanism, 2013-01-15; MS207.002.00822
      - Concerns and Complaints Submitted to JPSM Co-Chairs, 2013-01-18; MS207.002.00823
      - Concerns and Complaints Submitted to JPSM Co-Chairs, 2013-01-18; MS207.002.00824
      - Extraordinary Meeting of the Joint Political and Security Mechanism - decisions, 2013-01-18; MS207.002.00825
      - Extraordinary Meeting of the Joint Political and Security Mechanism, 2013-01-18; MS207.002.00826
    - Matrix, 2013; MS207.002.00827
      - Draft Implementation Matrix for Sudan - South Sudan Agreements, 2013-01-14; MS207.002.00828
      - Draft Implementation Matrix for Sudan - South Sudan Agreements, 2013-01-14; MS207.002.00829
      - Draft Agenda for LNP Meeting, 2013-01-17; MS207.002.00830
      - Draft Implementation Matrix for Sudan - South Sudan Agreements, 2013-01-17; MS207.002.00831
    - Meetings, 2012; MS207.002.00832
      - Key Points internal meeting matrix, 2012-01-14; MS207.002.00833
    - Questionnaire Letters, 2013; MS207.002.00834
      - AUHIP letter MPM FOC authorisation GoRSS, 2013-01-09; MS207.002.00835
      - AUHIP letter MPM FOC authorisation GoS, 2013-01-09; MS207.002.00836
      - AUHIP Letter to Dar Petroleum, 2013-01-09; MS207.002.00837
      - AUHIP Letter to Greater Nile Petroleum Operating Company, 2013-01-09; MS207.002.00838
      - AUHIP Letter to Greater Pioneer Operating Company, 2013-01-09; MS207.002.00839
      - AUHIP Letter to Petrodar, 2013-01-09; MS207.002.00840
      - AUHIP Letter to Sudd Petroleum Operating Company/White Nile Petroleum Operating Company, 2013-01-09; MS207.002.00841
    - Questionnaire responses, 2013; MS207.002.00842
      - Implementation "Agreements between the Government of the Republic of South Sudan and the Government of Sudan on Oil and Related economic matters", 2013-01-10; MS207.002.00843
      - Implementation "Agreements between the Government of the Republic of South Sudan and the Government of Sudan on Oil and Related economic matters", 2013-01-10; MS207.002.00844
      - Implementation "Agreements between the Government of the Republic of South Sudan and the Government of Sudan on Oil and Related economic matters", 2013-01-10; MS207.002.00845
      - Implementation "Agreements between the Government of the Republic of South Sudan and the Government of Sudan on Oil and Related economic matters", 2013-01-11; MS207.002.00846
      - Implementation "Agreements between the Government of the Republic of South Sudan and the Government of Sudan on Oil and Related economic matters", 2013-01-11; MS207.002.00847
    - Summit, 2013; MS207.002.00848
      - Summit between the Republic of Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan on Resolution of Outstanding Issues in Their Relations -Addis Ababa, 2013-01-24; MS207.002.00849
      - Tentative Schedule for AUHIP Meetings, 2013-01-25; MS207.002.00850
    - Two Areas, 2013; MS207.002.00851
      - Non-Paper on the Resolution of the Conflict in the Two Areas, 2013-01-25; MS207.002.00852
    - between the Republic of Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan - decisions and outcomes, 2012-01-15; MS207.002.00853
    - Draft Implementation Matrix for Sudan - South Sudan Agreements, 2013-01-03; MS207.002.00854
    - Summary of Views from Juba and Khartoum, 2013-01-03; MS207.002.00855
    - Summit Meeting between President Salva Kiir Mayardit and President Omar Hassan al Bashir Narrative agenda, 2013-01-03; MS207.002.00856
    - Summit Meeting between President Salva Kiir Mayardit and President Omar Hassan al Bashir Narrative agenda, 2013-01-03; MS207.002.00857
    - Summit Meeting between President Salva Kiir Mayardit and President Omar Hassan al Bashir Statement, 2013-01-03; MS207.002.00858
    - Summit Meeting between President Salva Kiir Mayardit and President Omar Hassan al Bashir Statement, 2013-01-03; MS207.002.00859
    - Continuation of Logistical and Financial Support to the AUHIP, 2013-01-15; MS207.002.00860
    - AUHIP Press Statement, 2013-01-19; MS207.002.00861
    - Report of the African Union High Level Implementation Panel for Sudan and South Sudan, 2013-01-21; MS207.002.00862
    - Report of the African Union High Level Implementation Panel for Sudan and South Sudan, 2013-01-22; MS207.002.00863
    - AUHIP Summit Details, 2013-01-23; MS207.002.00864
    - Draft Implementation Matrix for Sudan - South Sudan Agreements, 2013-01-24; MS207.002.00865
    - Report of the African Union High Level Implementation Panel for Sudan and South Sudan, 2013-01-25; MS207.002.00866
    - Report of the African Union High Level Implementation Panel for Sudan and South Sudan, 2013-01-25; MS207.002.00867
    - Report of the African Union High Level Implementation Panel for Sudan and South Sudan, 2013-01-25; MS207.002.00868
    - Draft Letter to President Bashir and cc President Kiir, 2013-01-28; MS207.002.00869
    - Draft AUHIP letter, 2013-02-01; MS207.002.00870
  - February 2013 negotiations, MS207.002.00871
    - Darfur, 2013; MS207.002.00872
      - A Sudanese Political Process, 2013-02-07; MS207.002.00873
      - Comments on strategy paper, 2013-02-19; MS207.002.00874
    - Two Areas, 2013; MS207.002.00875
      - AUHIP draft invite 2A extended GoS, 2013-02-11; MS207.002.00876
      - AUHIP draft invite 2A extended SPLMN, 2013-02-11; MS207.002.00877
      - AUHIP invite 2A brief, 2013-02-11; MS207.002.00878
    - Update on the current status in Sudan and South Sudan, 2013-02-12; MS207.002.00879
    - Political and Security Update, 2013-02-14; MS207.002.00880
    - Edited update on the current status in Sudan and South Sudan for President, 2013-02-14; MS207.002.00881
  - March 2013 negotiations, 2012 -- 2013; MS207.002.00882
    - Invitations, 2013; MS207.002.00883
      - AUHIP invite LNP GoRSS, 2013-02-08; MS207.002.00884
      - AUHIP invite JPSM GoRSS, 2013-02-28; MS207.002.00885
      - AUHIP invite JPSM GoRSS, 2013-02-28; MS207.002.00886
      - AUHIP invite JPSM GoS, 2013-02-28; MS207.002.00887
      - AUHIP invite JPSM GoS, 2013-02-28; MS207.002.00888
      - AUHIP invite LNP GoRSS, 2013-02-28; MS207.002.00889
      - AUHIP invite LNP GoS, 2013-02-28; MS207.002.00890
      - AUHIP invite LNP GoS, 2013-02-28; MS207.002.00891
      - AM Invite UNISFA FC, 2013-03-01; MS207.002.00892
      - AM Invite UNISFA FC, 2013-03-01; MS207.002.00893
      - AUHIP letter to Idriss Abdel Gader/GoS - date change LNP, 2013-03-03; MS207.002.00894
      - AUHIP letter to Idriss Abdel Gader/GoS - date change LNP, 2013-03-03; MS207.002.00895
      - AUHIP letter to GoS - date change Two Areas, 2013-03-03; MS207.002.00896
      - AUHIP letter to GoS - date change Two Areas, 2013-03-03; MS207.002.00897
      - AM letter to Paatii Ofosu Amaah/African Development Bank, 2013-03-04; MS207.002.00898
    - Joint Political and Security Mechanism, 2013; MS207.002.00899
      - Documents package, 2013; MS207.002.00900
        - Concerns and Complaints Submitted to JPSM Co-Chairs, 2013-01-18; MS207.002.00901
        - Extraordinary Meeting of the Joint Political and Security Mechanism between the Republic of Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan, 2013-03-08; MS207.002.00902
        - Security Matrix: Implementation Activities, 2013-03-08; MS207.002.00903
        - Implementation plan approved by the JPSM - Co-chairs on 19 December 2012 Updates with JBVMM Deployment Details Agreed on 8 March 2012 in Addis Ababa, 2013-03-08; MS207.002.00904
      - JPSM, 7 March 2013 Draft Annotated Agenda, 2013-03-05; MS207.002.00905
      - Implementation plan approved by the JPSM - Co-chairs on 19 December 2012 Updates with JBVMM Deployment Details Agreed on 8 March 2012 in Addis Ababa - Updated, 2013-03-06; MS207.002.00906
    - Joint Political and Security Mechanism 2, 2013; MS207.002.00907
      - Letters, 2013; MS207.002.00908
        - AUHIP transmission SK disengagement letter GoS AR, 2013-03-13; MS207.002.00909
      - Meetings, 2013; MS207.002.00910
        - JPSM, 2013-03-19; MS207.002.00911
        - JPSM Meeting on 18 March 2013, 2013-03-19; MS207.002.00912
      - Secretariat documents, 2013; MS207.002.00913
        - Terms of Reference: JPSM and JPSM Joint Secretariat, 2013-03-16; MS207.002.00915
        - Terms of Reference: JPSM and JPSM Joint Secretariat, 2013-03-19; MS207.002.00916
        - Example - Agenda for Meeting of the JPSM, 2013-03-16; MS207.002.00917
        - Example - Annotated Agenda for Meeting of the JPSM, 2013-03-16; MS207.002.00918
        - Example - Annotated Agenda for Meeting of the JPSM, 2013-03-16; MS207.002.00919
        - Extraordinary Meeting of the Joint Political and Security Mechanism (JPSM), 2013-03-16; MS207.002.00920
        - Concerns and Complaints Submitted to JPSM Co-Chairs, 2013-03-16; MS207.002.00921
        - Example - Decisions Adopted by the JPSM, 2013-03-16; MS207.002.00922
      - JPSM Workshop, 2013-03-16; MS207.002.00914
      - Annotated Agenda for Meeting of the JPSM be held in Addis Ababa on 17 March 2013, 2013-03-07; MS207.002.00923
      - Draft Agenda for Meeting of the JPSM be held in Addis Ababa on 17 March 2013, 2013-03-07; MS207.002.00924
      - AUHIP transmission SK disengagement letter GoS AR, 2013-03-09; MS207.002.00925
      - AUHIP invite JPSM GoRSS, 2013-03-13; MS207.002.00926
      - AUHIP invite JPSM GoRSS, 2013-03-13; MS207.002.00927
      - AUHIP invite JPSM GoS, 2013-03-13; MS207.002.00928
      - AUHIP invite JPSM GoS, 2013-03-13; MS207.002.00929
      - Draft Communique JPSM, 2013-03-20; MS207.002.00930
      - Report on the JPSM Meeting, 2013-03-20; MS207.002.00931
    - Logistics, 2012 -- 2013; MS207.002.00932
      - Negotiation TSU Comparison, 2012-08-17; MS207.002.00933
      - Participant List, 2013-03-02; MS207.002.00934
      - Participant List, 2013-03-04; MS207.002.00935
    - Matrix, 2013; MS207.002.00936
      - Timing Matrix draft 1, 2013-01-20; MS207.002.00937
      - Draft Implementation Matrix for Sudan - South Sudan Agreements, 2013-03-09; MS207.002.00938
      - Draft Implementation Matrix for Sudan - South Sudan Agreements, 2013-03-09; MS207.002.00939
      - Draft Integrated Implementation Matrix for Sudan - South Sudan Agreements, 2013-03-10; MS207.002.00940
      - Draft Implementation Matrix for Sudan - South Sudan Agreements, 2013-03-10; MS207.002.00941
      - Implementation Matrix for Agreements Between The Republic of the Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan, 2013-03-11; MS207.002.00942
      - AUHIP Draft Merged Implementation Matrix, 2013-03-11; MS207.002.00943
      - Implementation Matrix for Agreements Between The Republic of the Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan, 2013-03-12; MS207.002.00944
      - Adoption of Implementation Matrix By The Republic of the Sudan And The Republic of South Sudan, 2013-03-12; MS207.002.00945
    - Meetings, 2013; MS207.002.00946
      - Internal Meeting: Two Areas, 2013-03-06; MS207.002.00947
      - Internal Panel Meeting, 2013-03-07; MS207.002.00948
      - Technical Meeting - RSS, 2013-03-10; MS207.002.00949
    - Visas, 2013; MS207.002.00950
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Khalid Daraj, 2013-02-13; MS207.002.00951
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Neroun Ajo, 2013-02-16; MS207.002.00952
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Osman Adaroob, 2013-02-16; MS207.002.00953
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Simon Kalo, 2013-02-16; MS207.002.00954
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Yasir Arman, 2013-02-16; MS207.002.00955
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Zeinab Eldai, 2013-02-16; MS207.002.00956
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLM Abdella Ibrahim Abass, 2013-02-26; MS207.002.00957
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLM Hashim Orta Eldaw, 2013-02-26; MS207.002.00958
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLM Izdihar Juma, 2013-02-26; MS207.002.00959
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLM Waleed Hamed, 2013-02-26; MS207.002.00960
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Zeinab Eldai, 2013-02-26; MS207.002.00961
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Ahamed Abdelrahaman Saeed, 2013-02-26; MS207.002.00962
    - Curriculum Vitae Chakib Kkelil, 2012-11-13; MS207.002.00963
    - AM letter SPLMN postponement, 2013-03-14; MS207.002.00964
    - AUHIP letter AUC PMC Chair, 2013-03-14; MS207.002.00965
    - JPSM Checklist, 2013-03-26; MS207.002.00966
  - April 2013 negotiations, MS207.002.00967
    - Invitations, 2013; MS207.002.00968
      - Abdul Mohammed letter to Michael Makuei JBC, 2013-03-02; MS207.002.00969
      - AUHIP invite JPSM, 2013-03-02; MS207.002.00970
      - Abdul Mohammed letter to Michael Makuei JBC, 2013-03-03; MS207.002.00971
      - AUHIP invite JPSM, 2013-03-03; MS207.002.00972
      - AUHIP JCBC Contribution, 2013-04-03; MS207.002.00973
      - Abdul Mohammed request IGAD TSU, 2013-04-06; MS207.002.00974
      - AUHIP Invitation to GoS on Nationality, 2013-04-07; MS207.002.00975
      - AUHIP Invitation to RSS on Nationality, 2013-04-07; MS207.002.00976
      - AUHIP letter Gen. John Kong Dialogue, 2013-04-10; MS207.002.00977
      - AUHIP letter Gen. John Kong Dialogue, 2013-04-10; MS207.002.00978
      - AUHIP invite legal cluster GoS, 2013-04-11; MS207.002.00979
      - AUHIP invite legal cluster RSS, 2013-04-11; MS207.002.00980
      - AUHIP invite Malik Agar - draft, 2013-04-12; MS207.002.00981
      - AUHIP invite legal clusters, 2013-04-13; MS207.002.00982
      - AUHIP letter Dialogue - Malik Agar, 2013-04-13; MS207.002.00983
      - AUHIP letter Dialogue, 2013-04-13; MS207.002.00984
      - AUHIP invite Ibrahim Gandour - draft, 2013-04-14; MS207.002.00985
      - AUHIP invite Ibrahim Gandour, 2013-04-14; MS207.002.00986
      - AUHIP invite Malik Agar, 2013-04-14; MS207.002.00987
      - Abdul Mohammed request IGAD TSU, 2013-04-16; MS207.002.00988
      - Abdul Mohammed request IGAD TSU, 2013-04-16; MS207.002.00989
      - AUHIP invite Abdel Gadir, 2013-04-16; MS207.002.00990
      - AUHIP invite Amum, 2013-04-16; MS207.002.00991
      - AUHIP invite Amum, 2013-04-16; MS207.002.00992
      - AUHIP invite Abdel Gadir, 2013-04-16; MS207.002.00993
    - Joint Political and Security Mechanism: Corridors committee, 2013; MS207.002.00994
      - Corridors Between the Republic of Sudan (RoS) and the Republic of South Sudan (RoSS) into the Safe Demilitarised Border Zone (SDBZ), 2013-04-20; MS207.002.00995
      - Joint Technical Border Corridors Committee Between the Republic of Sudan (RoS) and the Republic of South Sudan (RoSS), 2013-04-20; MS207.002.00996
      - Report of the Joint Technical Border Corridors Committee Between the Republic of Sudan (RoS) and the Republic of South Sudan (RoSS), 2013-04-21; MS207.002.00997
    - Legal cluster, 2013; MS207.002.00998
      - Mechanism for Implementation, Monitoring, Evaluation and Dispute Resolution Relating to the Cooperation Agreement, 2013-04-19; MS207.002.00999
    - Meetings, 2013; MS207.002.01000
      - Two Areas Meeting 24 April 2013 5pm, 2013-04-24; MS207.002.01001
      - Two Areas Meeting, 2013-04-25; MS207.002.01002
    - Two areas, 2013; MS207.002.01003
      - Declaration of Common Intent for The Resolution of the Conflict in Blue Nile and Southern Kordofan States, 2013-04-24; MS207.002.01004
      - Declaration of Common Intent for The Resolution of the Conflict in Blue Nile and Southern Kordofan States, 2013-04-24; MS207.002.01005
      - Draft proposal for the Final Resolution and Settlement of the Conflict in Southern Kordofan and Blue Nile States, 2013-04-25; MS207.002.01006
      - Agreement on Humanitarian Access and Cessation of Hostilities for Southern Kordofan/Nuba Mountains/The Blue Nile States - SPLMN, 2013-04-26; MS207.002.01007
      - Agreement on Humanitarian Access and Cessation of Hostilities for Southern Kordofan/Nuba Mountains/The Blue Nile States - SPLMN, 2013-04-26; MS207.002.01008
    - Visas, 2013; MS207.002.01009
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN, 2013-04-18; MS207.002.01010
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Abdallah Ibrahim Abass, 2013-04-18; MS207.002.01011
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Ahmed Saeed, 2013-04-18; MS207.002.01012
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Hashim Aldaw, 2013-04-18; MS207.002.01013
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Izdihar Saeed, 2013-04-18; MS207.002.01014
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Khalid Daraja, 2013-04-18; MS207.002.01015
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Neroun Ajo, 2013-04-18; MS207.002.01016
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Osman Adroob, 2013-04-18; MS207.002.01017